Check the brake for unusual noise, heat or smell during normal operation.
檢查剎車在正常運作時有無異常噪音、熱度或氣味。
Make sure the elevator will not move.
確保電梯不會移動。
Remove the covers to get access to the brake and the brake drum.
拆下蓋子以便接觸到剎車和剎車鼓。
Check that the brake drum and linings are free of oil.
檢查剎車鼓和襯片是否沒有油污。
In case of contamination, clear away any contamination on all functional parts of the brake and inform your service leader.
如果有污染，清除剎車所有功能部件上的污染，並通知你的服務主管。
If one of the brake lining becomes oily, means oil spread on the brake drum, replace both brake shoe assemblies with the linings.
如果其中一個剎車襯片變得油膩，表示油已經擴散到剎車鼓上，需更換兩個剎車襯片組件。
If there is a risk of further oil contamination, install an oil wiper and schedule regular visits to monitor the situation until the root cause has been rectified.
如果有進一步油污染的風險，安裝油刮並安排定期檢查，直到根本原因得到解決。
Units with contaminated brake parts must never be left in operation.
有污染的剎車部件的單位絕不能繼續運行。
Check the wear of the brake lining and its fixation If any part of the lining is separated from the brake shoe, replace the whole brake shoe assembly with the lining.
檢查剎車襯片的磨損和固定情況，如果襯片的任何部分與剎車鞋分離，需更換整個剎車襯片組件。
The brake lining thickness must be 4mm or more Replace if it's below.
剎車襯片的厚度必須至少4毫米，否則需更換。
Check the support angle touches the brake shoe when the brake is closed If necessary, adjust the support angle.
檢查支撐角在剎車閉合時是否接觸到剎車鞋，如有需要，調整支撐角。
A correct setting will ensure a correct air gap between the brake lining and the drum during operation.
正確的設置將確保剎車襯片和剎車鼓之間在運行時有正確的空隙。
Check that all linkages, springs and nuts are secured and free from rust.
檢查所有連桿、彈簧和螺母是否固定牢固且無銹。
Remove the rubber O-ring carefully Sharp objects must not be used.
小心地取下橡膠O形圈，不能使用尖銳物品。
Measure the dimensions at the different air gap points on the brake magnet 1.2mm on the top, 1.1mm in the middle and 1mm at the bottom.
測量剎車磁鐵不同空隙點的尺寸，頂部1.2毫米，中間1.1毫米，底部1毫米。
Indications for incorrect air gaps is loud noise when the brake is applied Adjust if necessary and confirm correct operation.
空隙不正確的指示是剎車應用時的噪音很大，如有需要，調整並確認正確運行。
Check the O-ring and replace if it's not in good condition anymore The O-ring minimizes noise and prevent ingress of materials.
檢查O形圈，如果狀況不佳，需更換。O形圈可減少噪音並防止材料進入。
Depends on the production year a sealed sealing cap should be present Units with a bushing must have a sealed sealing cap with the brake closed.
根據生產年份，應有密封蓋。帶有軸套的單位在剎車閉合時必須有密封蓋。
Check that the KB actuating bracket just touched the contact plunger Adjust if necessary and check the correct function.
檢查KB啟動支架是否剛好接觸到接觸柱，如有需要，調整並檢查正確功能。
It's important that both contacts switch at the same time This can be checked with the help of a feeder gauge.
重要的是兩個接觸點同時切換，可以使用厚薄規來檢查。
In case of KB adjustments, always perform several trips and check that both KB switch and no brake errors are reported in the error lock.
如果需要調整KB，記得進行幾次測試，確保KB開關和剎車系統沒有報錯。
In case of any errors, check the details and repeat the KB adjustments.
如果有任何錯誤，檢查詳細信息，並重複進行KB調整。